<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <string name="app_name">Mood Mapper</string>
    <string name="no_mood">No moods added yet!\nClick the + to add something.</string>
    <string name="menu_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="button1">Review</string>
    <string name="button2">+</string>
    <string name="button3">-</string>
    <string name="button4">previous</string>
    <string name="button5">next</string>
    <string name="button6">Log without Trigger</string>
    <string name="review">Daily Review</string>
    <string name="history">History</string>
    <string name="about">About</string>
    <string name="new_list">New List</string>
    <string name="clear_list">Clear List</string>
    <string name="title_activity_about">General Info</string>
    <string name="howto_title">How to use:</string>
    <string name="howto_info">
        \tClick the \"+\" symbol in the upper right corner to add a new emotion to the list.
        Once added, it will appear as a button on the list for easy access. Use the \"–\" symbol to delete items 
        from the list that are no longer being used. \n\n
        
        \tIf the emotion you want to log is on your list, click it to create a log entry. A new list will 
        appear for you to populate with your common triggers\n\n
        
        \tClick “Review” to switch to Daily Review mode. This shows a timeline of all your emotions throughout the day. 
        To see past reviews, swipe left to go back in time one day, and right to go forward.</string>
    <string name="premises_header">Mapping Guidelines</string>
    <string name="premise1">1. Create your own emotions and triggers</string>
    <string name="premise1_text">\tInstead of using a pre-generated list of emotions or triggers, you are 
        encouraged to look within and discover what you feel for yourself, instead relying on cliche emotional 
        labels. Every emotion or trigger you add to the lists is saved for future use. As human beings, we tend 
        to exhibit habitual repetitive emotional patterns. By maintaining a saved list of individually 
        generated emotions and triggers, MoodMapper can aid us in discovering and understanding our habitual 
        patterns</string>
    <string name="premise2">2. Keep refining your emotion and trigger lists</string>
    <string name="premise2_text">\tEmotional awareness is not an easy task, but with practice we 
        are bound to improve at it. As your emotional discernment grows, be willing to clean up your lists 
        of unused or irrelevant items in order to see more clearly the repeating patterns. The idea is not to 
        collect as many emotions as possible, but to understand the patterns that drive us at a deep level.</string>
    <string name="premise3">3. Learn to recognize emotions by their \"flavor\"</string>
    <string name="premise3_text">\tEach emotion you add to the list should have its own distinct 
        \"flavor\". Often these "flavors" don\'t have a convenient label from everyday language that captures 
        all of their nuance. That is another reason for creating our own list of emotions instead of using 
        ready-made lists. The idea is to find a unique label for each distinct flavor of emotion you recognize. 
        Gradually these emotions that once seemed vague and unrecognizable, will become clear and familiar, 
        just as unfamiliar vocabulary gradually becomes known through repeated encounters, even without 
        looking it up.</string>
    <string name="hello_world">Hello world!</string>
    <string name="title_activity_daily_review">Daily Review</string>
    <string name="title_activity_trigger">Trigger List</string>
    <string name="empty_main">\tNo emotions entered yet, press the \"+\" to add a new 
        mood. For information about how to use this app, select \"about\" from the menu.</string>
    <string name="empty_trigger">Press the \"+\" to add a new trigger</string>
    <string name="empty_review">Nothing has been mapped for this date</string>

</resources>